productiontrax.com 2006-06-22

# Productiontrax.com: Privacy Policy

PRIVACY POLICY    
  
Productiontrax.com values your privacy, whether you just browse the Productiontrax.com Web Site ("Site"), use its services, or purchase tracks. We strive to keep our privacy practices in current with the highest standards on the Web. This privacy policy describes the kinds of information we collect, how we collect it, and how we use it.

**WHAT TYPES OF INFORMATION DOES PRODUCTIONTRAX.COM COLLECT FROM ME?**

**Personally Identifiable Information.** Personally identifiable information is information that identifies you as an individual, such as your name, mailing address, phone number, email address, credit card information and password ("Personally Identifiable Information"). We may collect Personally Identifiable Information from you when you (a) make a purchase from our site (b) register to become a member, (c) voluntarily provide it when you use the Site, (d) disclose it in a public area of the Site (such as a composer bio, message board or chat room) or (e) provide it when you communicate with us. **

Non-Personally Identifiable Information.

** Non-personally identifiable information is information that does not identify you as an individual ("Non-Personally Identifiable Information"). Non-Personally Identifiable Information includes information such as your browser type, the URL of the previous Web site you visited, the Web pages and advertisements you view or select, and the types of services you use. Non-Personally Identifiable Information also includes "Aggregate Information," which is described below in the section titled "How Do We Use Non-Personally Identifiable Information?" We may automatically collect certain types of Non-Personally Identifiable Information from you when you use the Site. We may also collect Non-Personally Identifiable Information from you that you voluntarily provide (such as information included in response to a questionnaire or survey) or post to a public area of the Site (such as a message board or chat room). **HOW DO WE COLLECT INFORMATION?

Cookies.

**A cookie is a message that is sent to your browser from a Web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. Our cookies do not contain Personally Identifiable Information, such as your email address. We use cookies solely to keep track of which shopping cart belongs to you when you shop on our site. We use cookies only for the operation of our Site. **

IP Address.

** An IP address is a number that is assigned to your computer automatically when you use the Internet. We may collect IP addresses for the purposes of systems administration, server problem diagnosis and to compile aggregate information (such as how many visitors logged on to the Site). When you visit a particular Web page on the Site, our servers log your IP address. Your IP address is not linked to your Personally Identifiable Information. IP addresses also help us to identify individual users within our live support system. **

Pixels.

** Pixels, also called clear GIFs, are invisible files on Web pages that you visit. If you visit a page on the Site that contains a Pixel, the Pixel communicates with your computer to determine, among other things, whether you have been to that page before or viewed a particular advertisement. We may use Pixels to serve advertising, enhance site functionality, and track usage of the Site. **HOW DO WE USE YOUR INFORMATION?

Personally Identifiable Information. 

**In general, we will not disclose your Personally Identifiable Information to third parties without your permission. If you make a purchase from our Site, we may use the Personally Identifiable Information you provide for shipping and billing purposes only, unless you expressly give us permission to use it for promotional and marketing purposes. In addition, if you purchase tracks from a composer, we may provide that composer with your Personally Identifiable Information to enable that composer to contact you or use for their internal record keeping. We may also use the Personally Identifiable Information you provide to (a) administer and manage your account, (b) pay commissions to you, (c) include you on our mailing lists and (d) advertise and promote our services. In addition, we may disclose your Personally Identifiable Information when we believe in good faith that it is required by any applicable law or legal process, or if we believe we need to disclose it to protect or enforce our rights or the rights of our members, users, or other third parties. Without limitation of the foregoing, we may disclose your information pursuant to our Intellectual Property Rights Policy to a third party that alleges you have infringed their intellectual property rights. We will never sell your personally identifiable information to anyone. **

Non-Personally Identifiable Information.

** We may disclose Non-Personally Identifiable Information in connection with improving the services we offer and facilitating our marketing efforts. In addition, we may combine your Non-Personally Identifiable Information that relates to your use of the Site with that of other users ("Aggregate Information") to determine which areas of the Site are most popular, and how our services are used. By collecting this Aggregate Information and analyzing it, we can use it to improve the Site. We may disclose Aggregate Information in connection with improving the services we offer and facilitating our marketing efforts. **WARNING ABOUT ONLINE DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION

Third Parties. 

**We do not control the privacy policies of our advertisers or other third parties that have Web sites linked to the Site. If you click on an advertisement or link, the privacy policies of the Web site that you link to will govern the use of your information by that Web site's operator. We assume no responsibility or liability for the actions of such third parties with respect to their use of your information or otherwise. Accordingly, make sure you are aware of and comfortable with the privacy policies of any third-party Web sites you link to. In addition, you should be aware that certain third-party services or Web sites (for example, Pay Pal, or if you click on a link to one of our partner's or member's Web site) that you link to from our Web site each have their own information collection practices and privacy policies. **

Disclosure Of Information In Public Areas.

** If you voluntarily disclose information in a public area of the Site, such as a chat room or message board, that information may be collected and used by a third party to send you unsolicited messages, advertisements or for other purposes. We do not control the actions of these third parties in public areas of the Site, so if you disclose information in a public area, you do so at your own risk. **

No Absolute Safeguards.

** Although we will use reasonable efforts to safeguard the privacy of your information, transmissions on the Internet cannot be made absolutely secure. Accordingly, we assume no responsibility or liability for disclosure of any of your information due to errors in transmission, unauthorized third-party access or other causes beyond our reasonable control. **

Children's Personally Identifiable Information

** We feel strongly about protecting the privacy of children. We encourage children to involve their parents in any interactive activity they participate in online. We will not knowingly collect or use any personal information from children we know to be under the age of thirteen. In addition, once we are notified we will delete any information in our databases that originates from a child under the age of thirteen.  
**  
WHAT OPTIONS DO I HAVE TO CONTROL THE USE OF MY PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION?** Receiving Communications And Opting Out. During the member registration process, you can "opt out" of receiving certain communications from us and our partners. If you are already registered, you can still "opt out" from receiving these communications by emailing us at [support@Productiontrax.com](mailto:support@productiontrax.com) or by accessing your account information screen. Correction And Deletion Of Information. You can obtain a copy of and request that we correct your Personally Identifiable Information by emailing us at [support@Productiontrax.com](mailto:support@productiontrax.com). For your protection, you will be required to provide proof of your identity to obtain a copy of your Personally Identifiable Information. If you desire, we will delete all of your Personally Identifiable Information (except for your transaction history) from our records upon your request. However, if you choose to delete your Personally Identifiable Information, you may not be able to access some areas of the Site. **YOUR ROLE IN PROTECTING YOUR PRIVACY** Please remember that protection of your privacy begins with you. You are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of any password you use to register, and you should always be careful and responsible whenever disclosing information online. **

Acceptance of Privacy Policy.

** If you use the Site, you are accepting the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy, and we will have the right to use your information as described in this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to have your information used in any of the ways described in this Privacy Policy, you must discontinue use of the Site. We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time. Your continued use of the Site after we either personally notify you or generally post such changes on the site will constitute your acceptance of those changes. If you have questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, please email us at [support@Productiontrax.com](mailto:support@productiontrax.com). 

* * *

Productiontrax.com is the world's first online royalty free production music and sound effects library of its kind, connecting composers and musicians to multimedia producers, directors, and filmmakers worldwide. All music tracks and sound effects on productiontrax.com are made available for royalty free use in film, television, video games, and other multimedia projects, sold at prices set by the composer. Finally, composers of library music can maintain complete control of their music while filmmakers obtain high quality, original music for their projects quickly and affordably. **

Browse Royalty Free Music by:

** Music Style/Genre | Film Genre | Emotion | Instrumentation

Home | About Us | Support | FAQ | Message Boards | Royalty Free Music Links & Resources | Composer Directory  
Terms of Service | End-User License | Intellectual Property Policy | Refund Policy | Privacy Policy

©Copyright 2004 by One Light Music Productions, Inc.
